I will tell you now about Scrapers.
Because for Scrapers we may use our input, our user passed a list of your addresses and
a process is for fire or rancid content script to collect links from the current page.
Obviously we need to validate your rows, remove duplicates and normalize or add authentication
tokens, especially for proxies.
And yeah, we can schedule the loans in a pool with configurable concurrency like free to
6 concurrent loans.
And there is an example, there is an upscraper, it's extractor for Bing.
So we see it from here, it's like an extension for local planning, how we can use it.
And even if you create this kind of app, it's very popular to sell it on an innovator
market.
So AL, all website images grabber, Chrome extensions, only $60 to sell it to sales.
Just dial a scraper and extractor Chrome extension for the seven sales.
So if you're just extract some numbers, phone numbers by the end, Google Maps, business
the scraper from codecracker extension is 164 sales.
Great.
And this is a scraper.
I love it.
Well, my favorite extensions, as you can see, it's for now turn on but it can obviously
use the extension for it, let me see the population, OK?
And OK.
So I will create a new folder and I will try to make a scraper.
I really love simple machine model, we see some extension here, but unfortunately it's
no longer a problem.
So in order to do that, I would actually recreate it.
So the first I will create a new folder, I will go to Chrome extension, open, download,
now go to a cursor, open folder is the known all and first I'll pass the address, so
we'll just copy it and I can ask some questions, but I will switch to agent's mode.
Let's shoot, I need to implement build, this is my own extension, OK, now we need to wait
until it's made and then after that we'll be able to see it.
So I have some development steps, and I create manifest, so the background, background service
for a careful normal management, build pop-up in life or is in direction, implement a
counter script, full ink extraction, we have filtering, folder and some download queue
and management, an options page for starting a bit, nice, we can as well add some integration
with cloud storage, especially when we want to synchronize everything or all the naming
grows like prefixes or suffixes or zero-peded counters, I will just make before this for
it, if I always do it, and there is some ethical and legal reminder, we cannot use this
extension like to bypass some paywalls, DRM, authentication, multiple sites, anyway that harms
availability, because you'll just act like a DDoS behavior, describe like private, personal,
data without any concerns, so you can always follow side terms of service and rabbits
when it's appropriate, so first if you obviously create a product structure, it will start
with manifest JSON, background service worker, and then make pop-up, so we see core hierarchy
that will be content, so this is the content script for ink extraction, there are some
options for a page because obviously not every website, like the same way, but you try
to detect, so we have some utilities like picky extraction, filter engine, name mask folder,
and some assets, and I think it's great, but I can build it, but after that I will just
remove the extension, because for now I don't want to use an icons, and there is obviously
the commentation that will be added to show us how we can test it out in our own web browser.
We see the old DDoS are complete, so we can use the code "C" to create a new code, and we can do it.
The old DDoS are complete, well it's within our content, more than 2,000 lines, so I will
try them now in the edges, this is the hierarchy we see, it created like all of the DDoS files,
and first I will just let some figure that I don't know properly, I need to add icons,
so please make a workaround, so I want to use someone to use icons for my purpose, so this
is how it can make, please make a workaround, so I want to use icons for my purpose to test
out in the browser, it should be working now, so we go back to my extension tab, and now
we just load and pack from the scratch, don't know at all, it's now working, so the first
thing I'm going to do, I will just spin that extension, and when it's pinned we see some
of the actually patterns, flip or file, so we can try to extract all of the links, folders,
and so I will just open for example some of the page, I can open new tab, I can go to
the toest story you remember, and now if I go to this I can try to, okay this is zero links,
maybe and we'll just close it first, you see your patterns, okay we can possibly to even use
the file, as if impossible to add some extension like a folder, here we can adjust our
down settings and file categories, but the problem is that it doesn't want to, I will use
Wikipedia, and when I go to this direction, you should have like largest population by
country, now we see India, and China, and here I, my like links found are not visible,
so we can just try to make, okay, so it doesn't detect automatically, I want to detect
automatically tables, like in Wikipedia, and extract to excel spreadsheet, it'll be a new
task for a new agent, so this way we can prevent for many more risk of hallucinations,
file is now fixed, because there was a problem an issue, I'll try to reload it, I'll press
loud and pack the game, and go to my extension, there are still some errors, maybe I'll
clear all first, and then load again, and when I have my extension, okay, I'm refreshing,
it seems to be working, I'll go to Wikipedia now, and now when I go here, see there's
like a, could not establish connection, error extracting tables, I will take it, and
okay, I will just use the data, because it's contextual, and try to ask about it, so now
it's investigation, the connection error, again, can't the script communication issue,
so it will try to look for a send message, first if the can't the script isn't ready,
so you improve the error handling, and make the folder queues, the improve extraction
logic, okay, that's interesting now, we can try extracting tables again, it says try the
normal method first, the first method is error handling, it just the null storage connection
when the script isn't ready, and there's even more flow feedback, and we can even make
the nine extraction functions, so now we just open the game, but first you want to reload
the extension, and yeah, actually this one is always popping up, I can always try to make
it, so now I'm in the word expression, now there is still found 19 tables, alright, now
we see 19 tables, it generated some of the context for that, that's great, and obviously
you can extract data this way, you don't mind, they're probably extracted not everything,
but we can adjust it and add some more functionality for it, because when I go to the word
population, you see tables found, you can export all of the hands, it will go with some
years, okay, so I think this one is not working like we supposed to, but maybe table one
or columns, like this is estimates, we have to find an idea, this is like used to mostly
pop away countries, and I think this one would work the best, so how we use it, and now
if I press it, I see the 10 most populated by the area obviously because the Singapore Bangladesh
implies time, we see that city, and this way we can easily extract information by building
our own scraper.